<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Abraham</title>
    <link>https://www.timabe.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tim Abraham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.timabe.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re all Grand Ol&#39; Flags!</title>
      <link>https://www.timabe.info/blog/2023-05-12-you-re-all-grand-ol-flags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.timabe.info/blog/2023-05-12-you-re-all-grand-ol-flags/</guid>
      <description>The other day I was trying to think of a good trivia question, and this one popped into my head:
What country’s flag has the most colors?
It’s a hard question, right? It’s easy to think of flags with two colors (Japan, China) and even easier to think of flags with three colors. In my head I can think of maybe one flag with 4 colors although I can’t think which country it belongs to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gambler’s Ruin: A Simple Explanation and Derivation</title>
      <link>https://www.timabe.info/blog/gamblers-ruin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.timabe.info/blog/gamblers-ruin/</guid>
      <description>I’ve recently had the itch to break out some textbooks and do a little math. Don’t ask me where that desire comes from, but I find working on math problems fun. A few years ago I bought a probability textbook, which I learned about through an Amazon review by my intellectual hero, Nassim Taleb (here’s the review). Since then it has mainly been sitting on my book shelf, but occasionally I leaf through it and try to refresh my memory on some concept or learn a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.timabe.info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.timabe.info/about/</guid>
      <description>Greetings!
I&amp;rsquo;m Tim Abraham, a Bay Area based data scientist, amateur cook, and lover of reading and learning new things. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working at Airbnb. Prior to that, I was the head of Analytics at expa, an early stage startup studio in San Francisco, and before that, I spent time at a company called StumbleUpon (remember that!?) and was a founding member of the Growth Data Science team at Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CodeRag</title>
      <link>https://www.timabe.info/cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.timabe.info/cooking/</guid>
      <description>Notes: This article originally appeared in CodeRag.
Code/Rag has always been more than just another online tech blog. We strive to be part of the tech community—serving an essential, fundamental look at what’s going on in the valley. It’s why our tagline is “Know Your Code.” We think a tech news publication should know the basics. Be the source. Get down to brass tacks. We can do that because we’re part of the very ecosystem we’re reporting on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
